A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Extradition Requisition and Rendition Files of Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Extraditions Requisitions and Renditions: Requisitions, 2010-2013., Extent: 8 cu. ft. (8 boxes) (Box Boxes 5-12)
  - Scott, Shawn Ivan, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Shahan, Ralph Junior, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Sheets, Matthew Scott, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Shipley, Michael Chad, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Shirey, Jamie Aaron, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Shumaker, Joshua Glenn, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Smalls, Latonya Denise, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Smith, David D., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Smith, Jessa Wilson, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Smith, Moneta Christine, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Smith, Thomas Leander, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Smithson, Quadir Naiyu-Gill, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Spradlin, Daniel R., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Steele, Kayla Shere, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Stivers, Eric Lee, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Summerville, Wiliam Clarence, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Tharrington, Crystal Rose, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Thomas, Jesse, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Tilley, Jason Dwayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Tolliver, James Edward, Jr., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Tomlin, Charles Anthony, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Tredway, Curtis Lee, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Truett, John Clifford, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Tucker, Evelyn Nicole, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Tucker, Sabrina Anne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Tucker, Shawn Christopher, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Upchurch, James Franklin, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - VanMetre, Bryan A., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Viney, Freddie M., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Vowell, Colby Everett, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Walker, Jeremiah Douglas, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Wallace, Iken, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - White, Linda, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Whitley, Kirby Jean, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Wiggins, Aaron Thomas, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Wiland, Matthew Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Wilder, Anthony Marques, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Williams, David Mohammed, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Williams, Kevin Shawn, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Williams, Robert Terrance, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Wood, Chasity Michelle, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Yancey, Kevin, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Yeboah, Samuel K. Sams, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Yountz, Dwain Mitchell, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Allah, Wakil Lutalo, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Alston, Ric Rashid, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Amin, Tariq Rashad, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Barry James, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, Steven Paul, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Artis, Shirl Jean 2013 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bah, Rafael Nigel, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Barbee, Marcus Jermaine, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Barbee, Marcus Jermaine, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Barr, Brian Keith, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Beck, Michael Wayne, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bochm, Dennis George, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bolden, Derek Maurice, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Boulware, Daquan Jamarl, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bunting, Francis Mckinley, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Buracker, Coty Sharee, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Burns, Erick Harold, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Burton, Kenneth Joseph, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Cameron, Kenneth John, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Cameron, Mathew Michael, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Carrol, Ivan Junior, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Carr, Shonna J., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Carrol, Robert Steven, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Cavins, Nicole Michelle, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Chang, Jang Min, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Che, Guo Liang, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Clarett, Jaime M., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Coite, Joseph Charles, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Coles, Kenneth Arnaz, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Combs, Brian Keith, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Copney, Angus Dion, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Craig, Terrance Michael, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Creech, Marvin Earl, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Creech, Marvin Earl, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Crump, Michael Roland, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Curtis, Jamal, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Davis, Melissa, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Donelson, Timothy Leon, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Ducker, Harold, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Dudley, John William, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Durham, Tyran Oneal, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Fairfax, Richard Anthony, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Ferguson, Michael Earl, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Goodman, Crystal Gail, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Goinz, Zachary Vanquail, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Goulette, Joan M., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Gonzales, Pedro Sanchez, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Grady, Karen Joe, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Green, Ryan Edward, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Greene, Haywood Leon, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Hagwood, Amous Tyrone, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Hall, Amanda L., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Hall, Christopher J., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Harlow, Stephanie Hope, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Harris, Cornelious, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Harvey, Thomas Matthew, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Hazelwood, William Michael, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Hedspeth, Mark David, Sr., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Henderson, Kimberly Lynn, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Hickman, Jamar Edjuan, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Hill, Terren L., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Hollyfield, Cynthia Anne, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Hranko, Shirley, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Hudson, Cardiaet, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Humble, Stephen Maxton, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Jones, Jether Maryland, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Jones, Keyana Kuane, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Jones, Matthew Steven, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Kidd, Michael Wayne, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - King, Rebecca Robin, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Ladd, Dennis Mitchell, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Light, Corneil, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Linaburg, Ronald Lee, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Linford, Jay Michael, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Livers, Jonathan, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Logan, Floyd William, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Louck, Jason Travis, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Maimon, Steven Ralph, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Mainor, Anthony Tyrone, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Marion, Michelle Rae, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Mckenzie, Ashley Tilley, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - McLeroy, Samantha Karen, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - McNeill, Demetrios Deonte, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Mejia, Anderson Rivas, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Metz, Preston Miles, Jr., 2013 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Minitrez-Clark, Jennifer Angel, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Montenegro, Walter, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Monzon, Roman Sebastian, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Nelson, Cody, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Nofsinger, Richard Denny, Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - O'Marrah, Melinda Gayle, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ocana, Edwin, Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Owen, Keith Wayne, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Palmer, James Dion, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Parks, Jamie Lee, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Payne, Jonathan Mycal, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pinckney, Andre Maurice, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Porter, Byron Lee, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Price, Eric James, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Prioleau, Samuel, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Pritchett, Ashley Lamont, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Prudente, Amy Burrow, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Pruett, Chester W.M., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Rawlins, James Conrad, Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Reap, Christopher Michael, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Redd, Chanton Lamonte, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Reid, Terra Lenae, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Richards, Robert Thomas, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Rieve, Heather, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Roberts, Erin Londale, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Robertson, Jason Montgomerry, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Robish, Daniel John, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Rogers, Robert, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Russ, Natashia Maria, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sagadraca, Laureano M., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Saunders, Marvin Lewis, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Sciarabba, Eric, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Seese, Tina Marie, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Shane, Michael Gregory, Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Shortt, Joshua Lyle, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Shreffler, Norman Kenneth, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Simenton, Stephen Sterling, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Sisavat, Lee, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Slade, Huston David, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Smith, Antonio Raymond, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Sneed, William Christopher, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Snyder, Crystal M., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Speller, Terry Lamont, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Stanley, Jason Matthew, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Staruch, Jason Edward, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Stout, Amber Michelle, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Stottlemeyer, Ercy Theodore, Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Suber, Betty, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Tarleton, Anthony Allen, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Taylor, Brad Elliot, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Taylor, Troy Desmond, Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Tennett, Kelly Nicole, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Terry, John T., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Thompson, Victor C., Jr., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Tipton, Sarah Marie, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Tolliver, Christopher Jonathan, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Tolliver, Douglas Jason, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Tomaszewski, Richard L., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Torres, Michael Angel, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Trayham, William Lamont, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Trumball, Kimberly Ann, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Turcios, Leonel Antonio, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Upchurch, Jordan Taylor, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Vaden, Ricky Dale, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Vandiver, Troy Lee, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Vann, Maurice, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Verellan, Aris Christopher, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Waldron, Rondell Antonio, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Ward, Nathan, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Washington, Dalonte A., 2013 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Washington, Dameon Lee, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Washington, Ebony Fallon, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Watkins, Christopher Donnell, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Weberg, Christopher Scott, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - White, Dwayne Todd, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - White, John Franklin, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - White, Katina White, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Williams, Cleon Orlandes, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Williamson, Levi Tawand, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Witherspoon, Lamont Jason, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Wyatt, Bobby Gene, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Wynn, Antoine Omar, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Yarborough, Morris Tyrick, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 80)